A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1959-1960, 1; 19 Cubic Feet
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ger), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gi), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gin), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gl), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Go), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gon), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gor), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gov), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gr), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gray), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gre), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gren), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gu), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1959; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1959; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 245)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 246)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ha), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 247)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hag), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 248)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hal), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 249)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Halp), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ham), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 251)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hamm), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 252)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Han), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 253)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Har), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 254)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Harm), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hart), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Has), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 257)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hat), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 258)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hav), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 259)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Haw), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 260)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hay), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 261)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Haym), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 262)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Haz), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 263)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 264)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Heb), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 265)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hei), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 266)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hel), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 267)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hem), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 268)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hen), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 269)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Her), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 270)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hew), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 271)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 272)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hil), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 273)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hin), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 274)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hir), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 275)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hit), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 276)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1960 (Box 5, Folder 277)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hog), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hol), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Holl), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hom), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hoo), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hop), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hor), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hou), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (How), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hoy), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 288)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Huf), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 289)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hun), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hur), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hus), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hy), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 294)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Jo), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 296)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ju), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 298)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Jae), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Je), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ji), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Johns), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ke), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ki), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ko), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ku), 1959 (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kal), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kar), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ke), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kenm), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kent), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ker), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ki), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kir), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kn), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ko), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kr), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ku), 1960 (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 322)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 323)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 324)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 325)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 326)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (May), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 327)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 328)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McCo), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 329)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McD), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 330)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McG), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 331)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McK), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 332)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McN), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 333)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 334)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Men), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 335)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mer), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 336)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mes), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 337)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 338)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Miller), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 339)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Miller, J.), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 340)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Millm), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 341)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Min), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 342)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mit), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 343)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 344)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mont), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 345)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Moo), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 346)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mor), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 347)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Morr), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 348)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Morse), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 349)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mos), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 350)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 351)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (My), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 352)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 353)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ne), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 354)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ni), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 355)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (No), 1959 (Box 7, Folder 356)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 357)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ne), 1960 (Box 7, Folder 358)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ni), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (No), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 360)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Nu), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 361)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Op), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ot), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 364)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ob), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 366)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Oc), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 367)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Od), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 368)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Og), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ol), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 370)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Om), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 371)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (On), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Or), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 373)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ork), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 374)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Os), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 375)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ost), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 376)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ot), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ou), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ow), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pe), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pi), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Po), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pu), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pag), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 386)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Par), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 387)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pas), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 388)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pat), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 389)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pau), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 390)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pay), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pe), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 392)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pen), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Per), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 394)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pet), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 395)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pf), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 396)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ph), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 397)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pi), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 398)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pl), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 399)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Po), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pot), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 401)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pr), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 402)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pu), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 403)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 404)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1959 (Box 8, Folder 405)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Re), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 407)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ri), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 409)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rai), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 412)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ram), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 413)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Re), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 414)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rei), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rel), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 416)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rh), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 417)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ri), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 418)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rid), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 419)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rob), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 420)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rod), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 421)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rot), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 422)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ros), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 423)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1960 (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 425)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sch), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 426)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 427)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 428)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1959; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 429)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1959; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 430)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Su), 1959 (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 432)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (San), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 433)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sar), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 434)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sc), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 435)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Schin), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 436)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Scho), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 437)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sci), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 439)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sh), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 440)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (She), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 441)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Shi), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 442)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sho), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 443)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Shu), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 444)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 445)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sk), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 446)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sm), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 447)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Smith, F.), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 448)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Smy), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 449)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sn), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 450)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 451)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sp), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 452)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (St), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 453)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ste), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 454)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sti), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 455)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sto), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 456)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Stra), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 457)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Stu), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 458)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Su), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 459)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sw), 1960 (Box 10, Folder 460)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Te), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (To), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tu), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Te), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Th), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (To), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tr), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tu), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 472)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tw), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 473)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ty), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 474)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ve), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Vi), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Vo), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ve), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Vi), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 482)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Vo), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 483)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 484)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 485)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wi), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 486)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wo), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 487)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wu), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 488)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 489)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wal), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 490)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (War), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 491)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 492)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wes), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 493)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wet), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 494)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wh), 1960 (Box 11, Folder 495)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wi), 1960; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 496)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wi), 1960; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Win), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 498)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wis), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wit), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 500)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wo), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 501)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wr), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 502)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wu), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 503)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wy), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 504)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (X), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 505)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 506)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 507)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 508)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 509)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ab), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ba), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - New York State Correspondence (Be), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - New York State Correspondence (Bi), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - New York State Correspondence (Bo), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 514)
  - New York State Correspondence (Bu), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ca), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ce), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 517)
  - New York State Correspondence (Cl), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - New York State Correspondence (Co), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 519)
  - New York State Correspondence (Cu), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - New York State Correspondence (Da), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 521)
  - New York State Correspondence (De), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 522)
  - New York State Correspondence (Di), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 523)
  - New York State Correspondence (E), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 524)
  - New York State Correspondence (Fe), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 525)
  - New York State Correspondence (Fi), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 526)
  - New York State Correspondence (Fo), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 527)
  - New York State Correspondence (Fu), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 528)